[{"answer": "They stole my car", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "They did", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Sure", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Yes I did", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Did you steal my car", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You did?", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yes I did", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "I did", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "That's my car", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What are you gonna do with it", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Yeah, who's this", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Hello, my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I didn't cross any wires, the keys were in it", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Well, I was just watching them film yesterday and some guy just asked me", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Clear blue sky", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Yes, we do, unfortunately we ran out of cars", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I know why we have reservations", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What's an extremity", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "You raise the head, you get blood to the feet", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "You know what, let's put a few cookies in a blender and he could drink it", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Yes they do, you can liquefy a cookie", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Aw, you should see his bathrobe, man, it's all silk", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "He does, how'd you know that", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Moving cars from one side of the street to the other don't take no more sense than putting on a pair of pants. My question to you is who's putting your pants on", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "I don't believe you. If you can put your pants on, you can move those cars", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "So listen, what should I do? I mean if I break up with him now it'll look like I'm abandoning him because of his condition, I'll be ostracized from the community", "docId": "Seinfeld-The-Alternate-Side.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Of course there's a community", "qsentId": 28}]